<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UVa CSGSG</title>
    <link>//csgsg.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on UVa CSGSG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 09:56:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//csgsg.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CSGSG 2018 Election</title>
      <link>//csgsg.org/election/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 09:56:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//csgsg.org/election/</guid>
      <description>We have started the CS Graduate Student Group Steering Committee (CSGSGSC) 2018 election! Look forward to a new group of officers serving our community soon.
Voting We have started voting on December 4, 2018 till 11:59pm Friday, 12/07/2018.
Click to vote   Election Campaign      Candidate Nomination Any member of the CSGSG is eligible for nomination to CSGSGSC, provided he/she receives at least one nomination from either a member of the CSGSG (may be the nominee her/himself) or faculty from the Department of Computer Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Virtual Symposium 2020</title>
      <link>//csgsg.org/symposium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 12:36:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//csgsg.org/symposium/</guid>
      <description>Date: Friday, June 5th 2020, 9:00am - 5:30pm
Zoom Link: https://virginia.zoom.us/j/92206525927
Meeting ID: 922 0652 5927
Symposium Overview
As a result of the pandemic, CSGSG is hosting a CS Department Virtual Research Symposium on June 5th. The symposium is meant to allow everyone to learn about each other’s research and boost morale. The symposium will feature faculty introduction talks and short student research presentations for each of the core CS research areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symposium Summer 2020 Bios</title>
      <link>//csgsg.org/sympbios/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 12:36:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//csgsg.org/sympbios/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Graduate Student Lounge</title>
      <link>//csgsg.org/lounge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 12:36:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//csgsg.org/lounge/</guid>
      <description>The CS Graduate Student Lounge is room Rice 436. Feel free to use this space when taking a break from the gruelling working hours of the day. Have lunch with your friends (real or imaginary), hold philosophical discussion (&amp;ldquo;What is meaning of life?&amp;rdquo;), or try and find zen (if you believe it exists).
Location: Rice 436
P.S. If you have any cool ideas of how to make the lounge more comfortable (like adding board games etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UVa CS Tea Time</title>
      <link>//csgsg.org/teatime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 09:56:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//csgsg.org/teatime/</guid>
      <description>©Tango   Tea time is a great chance to talk with other people in the department! We offer free food and drink every week. Please consider hosting tea time if you enjoy the event.
Schedule The tea time schedule is available on the front page: https://csgsg.org.
How to host tea time  Please contact TeaTime Czar if you volunteer to host tea time. You may order food and drinks by phone, on the Internet or visiting the restaurants/stores in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About CSGSG</title>
      <link>//csgsg.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 23:00:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//csgsg.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The CSGSG serves as the assembly of all graduate students in the Department of Computer Science at the University of Virginia. All graduate students, Master’s and PhD, within the department of computer science or in the computer engineering program are automatically members of the CSGSG.
What we do? The goals of the CSGSG are to represent the CS/CPE graduate student body as well as serve as a mechanism for students to organize events including orientations, tea time, reading groups, and external events like hiking and picnics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>//csgsg.org/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 17:19:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//csgsg.org/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Write something here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>